Previously on...
前情提要
He's in your band. This is too dangerous.
他和你在一个乐队  这样太危险了
There were victims of both violence
暴力事件跟艰难时局
and hard times.
各有各的受害者
We're sort of broke.
我们差不多破产了
I thought Scavo's was doing well.
我以为斯加沃一家经营得不错呢
When times get tough,
经济不景气
people do without things like pizza.
人们不吃披萨也将就了
And beneficiaries...
也有受益者
The deal closed. I got the bonus.
交易结束  我拿到奖金了
And good work...
还有好工作
And perseverance.
跟不屈不挠的精神
Congratulations on your new job.
恭喜你有了新工作
Congratulations on getting me out of your office.
恭喜您成功把我赶出您办公室
It's not hard
要认出
to spot a mother who works outside the home.
一位有工作的母亲并不困难
Just look for someone who dresses in a hurry...
只要找找  哪些人匆匆忙忙地穿衣服
eats her breakfast while rushing to her car...
吃着早饭冲向车子
and applies her makeup as she drives away.
开车离开的时候还在化妆
But the surest way
不过要认出外出工作的母亲
to spot a mother who works outside the home?
最佳方法是什么呢
Just look for a child...
只要找到那个
M.J., why aren't you dressed?
M.J.  你怎么没有换衣服
We're gonna be late for our first day of school.
我们第一天去学校会迟到的
who gets sick at the worst possible moment.
在关键时刻生病的孩子
Hey, guys. How you doing?
早上好
He's sick. I'm late. Thanks for helping.
他生病了  我迟到了  谢谢帮忙
Whoa, whoa, whoa. I gotta work. So do I,
等等  我有工开  我也是
and it's my first day at a new job. I win.
今天我第一天开工  我赢
What...
什么
Look, I'd really like to help you out...
我真的很想帮你
and spend some time with my best bud, but, uh,
也很想陪陪我的好儿子
Ms. Nelson's septic tank is expecting me at 9:00.
可九点钟  我要去修纳尔逊小姐的化粪池
You're a plumber. Ms. Nelson is not expecting you on time.
你是个水管工  纳尔逊小姐不会指望你准时的
In fact, if you show up before dinner, she'll turn cartwheels.
事实上  要是你晚饭前到  她就乐得不行了
I'm a teacher. It's different.
我是老师  不能耽搁
Wait, I thought you were just a teacher's assistant.
你不过是助教而已
Listen to me.
听我说
The whole reason I went back to work is so we could both afford
我去那儿工作的唯一目的就是
to give M.J. the things we felt he needed.
给M.J.提供  我们认为他需要的一切
Now I'm doing my part. It's time you do yours.
我在尽我的责任  是你该表现的时候了
I'll reschedule Ms. Nelson.
那我和纳尔逊小姐再约
I gotta go.
我得走了
You get lots of rest and drink plenty of fluids, okay?
你要多休息多喝水  好吗
You never left me when I'm sick before.
你从没在我生病的时候离开过
Oh, I know, honey.
亲爱的  我知道
But mommy has a job now.
但现在妈妈要去工作
Come on. We talked about this. You understand, right?
好啦  我们谈过这个问题  你理解妈妈的吧
Don't be sad.
别难过
I am gonna pick you both up at 6:00.
我六点来接你们俩
Yes, it's not hard
是的  认出外出工作的母亲
to spot a mother who works outside the home.
并不是很困难
Just look for a woman
看看哪个女人
who leaves her house every morning
每天早晨离家的时候
feeling incredibly guilty.
带着极度的内疚就是了
It begins just after sundown,
夕阳西沉
after a long day at the office,
人们结束了一整天的工作
exhausted people start coming home.
疲惫不堪  回到家中
Some are met by faithful pets...
迎接自己的是忠实的宠物
Some are welcomed with dry martinis.
或者是干马丁尼酒
Others are greeted with dinner on the table.
或者是美妙的晚餐
Then there are those
也有些人
who return from a long day at work...
下了班回到家
only to discover...
却只发现
unpleasant surprises.
不愉快的意外
Oh! Good. You got my note. Come on in.
太好了  你看到我的字条了  快进来
Okay, sure. Uh, where's M.J.?
是的  M.J.呢
Here I am, mommy.
妈妈  我在这儿呢
Oh, hey, baby. How's my boy?
儿子  感觉怎么样
I missed you so much.
我好想你啊
Are you feeling better?
有没有觉得好点儿啦
Yeah. Katherine made me soup
好多了  凯瑟琳给我做了汤
and read me a story
给我讲了个故事
and showed me how to play blackjack.
还教了我玩儿21点
What are you gonna remember?
要记得什么啊
Always double down on a pair of aces.
有一对A就加倍下注
That's cute.
真棒
Where's Mike?
麦克上哪儿了
Plumbing emergency.
水管工的紧急状况
Ms. Nelson's toilet began erupting,
纳尔逊小姐的厕所系统崩溃了
and I wasn't busy, so...
正好我有空
Well, uh, thank you very much for helping us out.
谢谢你帮忙
Come on, M.J. It's time to go.
M.J.  我们该回家了
Thank you.
谢谢你
We already thanked her, buddy.
儿子  我们已经谢过她了
Let's not make her uncomfortable.
不要再麻烦人家了
Thank you for having us over.
谢谢你邀请我们过来
We are so honored
能成为你们新家的第一批客人
to be the first guests in your new home.
我们深感荣幸
Your stunning new home. I can't believe this.
你们的新房子真是太棒了  真难以相信
The theme of my first place was early American beanbag.
我的第一个家可不怎么样
Well, it's all Andrew.
都是安德鲁
He's the one with the taste, please.
他才是那个有品位的人
Uh, he's running late.
他迟到了
Um, do you know why?
你们知道是怎么回事吗
Ah,he's cleaning up a little mess.
有点小麻烦他要处理
Someone didn't know you couldn't serve
有人不知道犹太男孩儿成人仪式上
bacon-wrapped shrimp puffs at a bar mitzvah.
不能吃熏肉虾馅儿的泡芙
I knew. I just thought if they'd tasted mine,
我知道  我只是认为他们吃了我做的
they might change the rules.
也许就会改变这规矩了
So would you like something to nibble on before dinner?
晚饭前  你们要不要吃点什么
Is that cut crystal?
是水晶吗
It's exquisite.
精美之极
Andrew again. He's got expensive taste.
也是安德鲁选的  他的品味可不便宜
Thank god he brings in the big bucks.
多亏他有钱了
He does?
有钱了
Well, he does now, ever since you gave him that raise.
是啊  多亏您给他加薪
This is a delicious snack.
这种点心真美味
Did you make this?
是你做的吗
Uh, yeah. it's just...
是的  只是
party mix.
派对什锦罢了
You gave Andrew a raise?
-你给安德鲁加薪了
A tiny salary bump.
加了一点儿
"Tiny" is not the word for your extraordinary generosity.
非常慷慨  可不是"一点儿"啊
Oh, look! There's pretzels and cereal.
看看  这儿既有椒盐卷饼也有麦片
I can see why they call it "party mix."
难怪叫做"派对什锦"
It's like a party in a bowl.
就像碗里开了派对
When you say "extraordinary"-- he's exaggerating.
你说的"非常"  他只是夸张
They're children.
他们还是孩子
It just looks like a lot of money to them.
对他们来说就是一大笔钱
My god! Is this a... '96 Latour?
天哪  这是不是96年份的拉图尔
I know. Andrew bought a case of it
我知道  安德鲁在一次
At a wine auction
葡萄酒拍卖会上买了一箱
to celebrate that huge raise.
为庆祝他的大加薪
Once you've had a few glasses of this,
你只要喝上几杯这酒
you're not going to remember this evening at all.
今晚的事儿就都不记得啦
We'll see.
等着瞧吧
Boy, dinner without the kids...
天哪  没有孩子的晚餐
It's nice to eat without having macaroni thrown at you.
吃饭时没被通心粉砸  这可真棒
Yes.
是的
Well, we, uh, we really wanted to find a way
我们真得好好地
to thank you both.
-谢谢你们俩
Thank us for what?
谢什么
Saving our marriage.
挽救了我们的婚姻
Please. It was our pleasure.
拜托  这是我们的荣幸
How did we do that again?
我们是怎么帮你们的来着
Well, Bradley had been working around the clock,
布莱德利一直夜以继日地忙工作
and I was feeling neglected.
我觉得自己被忽视了
But things are different now that he has Carlos.
但是他有了卡洛斯帮忙后就完全不同了
We have never felt closer.
我们从没如此亲密过
And, Gaby, I know I've been relying on Carlos a lot.
加布  我知道最近我全靠卡洛斯了
I- I hope it's not a problem, his being away from home so much.
希望没有给你造成困扰  他总是在外工作
Oh, I'll be more willing to forgive
只要他拿回奖金支票
once his bonus check comes in.
-我很愿意谅解的
and the only person
唯一一个
more excited than Gaby about that bonus is her jeweler.
比加布还为奖金激动的  就是她的珠宝商了
Brad, don't. It's been such a nice night.
布莱德  别这样  这样一个美好的夜晚
He's gonna hear it tomorrow anyway.
他明天还是要知道的
Hear what?
知道什么
Look, I'm sorry,
真抱歉
But we're forgoing bonuses this year.
今年我们没有奖金了
Can I get anyone dessert?
要上点心吗
Beat it. what?
走开  你说什么
It's the economy.
经济形势不太好
Um, our C.F.O. feels we need to do some belt tightening.
财务总监认为我们需要缩减开支
But do you know how much overtime Carlos has pulled?
你知道卡洛斯加了多少班吗
How many trips he's taken? He's killed himself.
他出了多少趟差  他已经拼上性命了
For god sakes, don't do this to my jeweler.
看在老天的份儿上  别这样对我的珠宝商
But, Gaby, no one's getting a bonus, not even Brad.
加布  没人有奖金的  布莱德也一样
So this was his bonus? A salad and a stuffed chicken breast?
那这就是他的奖金了  沙拉和鸡胸肉卷吗
Look, hopefully next year will be better.
明年的形势有希望会好一些
We're ready for dessert now.
上点心吧
Wrap up ten lobsters to go.
十个龙虾带走
Tom?
汤姆
Come here.
过来
We haven't had a customer in about a half an hour,
已经半个小时没有客人了
so maybe we should just...
也许我们应该
close up early.
早点收工
No. I got an idea.
别  我有主意了
Hey, everybody, hey, take off your aprons
伙计们  把围裙脱了
and come sit near the window.
到靠窗的位子坐着
What is this? It's called psychology.
什么意思  这叫心理战术
Come on! Hey! Guys...
快点儿
Nobody wants to eat in an empty restaurant, right?
没人喜欢在空荡荡的餐馆吃饭
So, guys, this is what we are gonna do.
所以这就是我们要做的
As soon as you see someone go by,
一看见有人经过
You laugh, act like you're having a great time.
你们放声大笑  表现出你们的愉快
It'll draw them in.
这样会把他们吸引来的
So now we have pretend customers?
现在我们是有饭托了
Gee, let's think of something to do
我们得想想
with all the pretend money we're gonna make.
怎么装作能赚到钱的样子
Trust me. This is gonna work.
相信我  会有用的
You're a group of old high school buddies.
你们是高中的老同学
You haven't seen each other since the big game.
自从高考后就没见面了
And you two-- you're on a hot date, okay?
你们俩在甜蜜的约会中
All right.
好了
Hey, look! There's somebody! Laugh! Have a great time.
有人了  快笑  开心地笑
Awesome. Just like that.
太棒了  就那样儿
As much as I love Tommy Scavo's improv theater,
尽管我很喜欢汤姆·斯加沃剧院
we need to face some facts here. It's a slump.
我们还得面对现实  经济衰退了
We--we--we--we'll ride it out. We've done it before.
能挺过去的  我们以前成功过的
We-- it's not a slump.
不是衰退
In this economy, people aren't eating out as much.
这样的经济形势下  人们不常出来吃饭
between that and Porter's legal bills
而且波特的诉讼费还等着付
and paying Bree back,
还得还布里钱
We are about a week away from going bankrupt.
再过一周我们就会破产了
Honey, please, have a little faith.
亲爱的  你得有信心
I did, for seven years.
我有  七年都有
Now I'm gonna be a realist, and I need you to be one, too.
现在我要现实点  你也得这样
Okay, I understand. you're worried. I am, too.
我明白  你很担心  我也是
But we can make it. We just have to be creative.
不过我们会熬过去的  我们得创新
But-- if we sell this place now,
但是假如我们现在把餐馆卖掉了
we can escape with some dignity and maybe even some money.
我们能体面的退出  甚至还能剩点钱
But if we keep on going like we are,
但是如果我们一直这样下去
we're gonna lose everything.
我们会失去一切的
No!
不会的
No.
不行
I am not going out like this.
我不能就这样离开
I am not gonna be a failure.
我不会失败的
Please tell me that they just saw customers.
拜托你告诉我  他们刚看见顾客了
So with all the calories we just burned,
为了我们刚消耗的那些卡路里
I say we deserve a huge lunch at a fancy restaurant.
我得说  来顿饭店大餐是我们应得的
You do like to live well, honey.
你确实喜欢奢华的生活呢  亲爱的
Well, why not? life is brief and mostly sucks.
干吗不呢  生命如此短暂  大部分都很无趣
Gotta grab all the good you can
在这尘嚣之上
While you're on this side of the dirt.
你得抓紧所有能抓到的美好
That was very poetic.
说的真有诗意
But sure, we'll go any place you want.
当然没问题  你想去哪我们都去
Mmm! that was easy.
那就简单了
Well, since I'm on a roll, how about this?
既然我说着算  这样如何
Let's go away this weekend--
咱们这周末出去
Pick a five-star hotel with a great spa and just live it up.
选个带SPA的五星级酒店  潇洒一把
I don't know about that.
我不知道哎
I've got a lot of stuff I need to do.
我还有好多事要做呢
Oh, come on.
得了
Big fluffy robes, long massages.
宽大蓬松的睡袍  长时间的按摩
Do you hear that?
你听到了吗
That buzzing.
这嗡嗡声
Uh... no, I don't hear anything.
不  我什么也没听到
Oh, maybe it--it's-- shh! shh!
也许是  嘘  嘘
I hear it up here sometimes.
我听到在这上面
What the hell is it?
到底是什么啊
Hey, you know what?
知道吗
I kind of like that hotel idea.
我有点喜欢这酒店的提议
Really?
真的吗
Yeah. you were right. life is brief.
是啊  你是对的  生命如此短暂
Why don't you go call the travel agent and see what's available?
你干吗不打给旅行社  问问有什么可以参加的
You know, you're kinda sexy when you buckle.
你知道  你让步时还挺性感的哦
I'm gonna call right now.
我现在就打电话
Dr. heller? listen, I got your latest text,
海勒医生  听着  我收到你的上条消息了
But you know, it's been a few weeks now,
可你知道  已经好几周了
And people are freaking out about you being gone so long.
你走了这么久  人们都要抓狂了
So now there's a staff meeting on the 15th,
15号有个员工大会
And if you're not back by then, I'm just gonna
要是你还没回来  我就必须
Have to tell people that I don't know where you are.
告诉大家  我不知道你的去向了
So will you please just call me?
所以你能给我打给电话吗
Hey, mike. how's it going?
嘿  麦克  你怎么样
Well, so far, I've broken off
目前为止  我已经弄坏
Three of these stupid plastic sprinkler heads.
三个这种愚蠢的塑料喷头了
But other than that, I'm great.
除了这个  我挺好
Well, good. look, I was coming over to ask,
好吧  听着  我过来是想问
What would you and katherine think about going camping?
你跟凯瑟琳  觉得出去野营怎么样
Oh, man, I love camping. when?
伙计  我超爱野营  什么时候去啊
Well, my schedule gets busy on the 15th,
我15号以后就很忙了
So it would have to be before then.
所以必须安排在那之前
I don't know, this weekend?
-我不知道  这周末行吗
oh, I'm definitely up for it.
我肯定没问题
Uh, I'm not sure if katherine will be.
我不知道凯瑟琳行不行
Well, if she doesn't go, then edie won't go, and...
要是她不去  伊迪也不会去的
Well, I guess if katherine knows another girl's coming,
好吧  我想要是凯瑟琳知道还有女孩要去
Maybe I can convince her. good.
-我能说服她去的  很好
Tell her the menfolk will do all the hard work--
告诉她男人会把所有粗活儿都干了
Build the fires, dig the latrines.
升火  挖厕坑
Hey, I wouldn't mention that, uh, latrine part
在我们到营地前
Until we're actually at the campsite.
我不会说起那个  厕坑的部分的
That's a good point.
说的好
I'll, uh, dig my gear out tonight. it's gonna be fun.
我把我的装备今晚找出来  一定会很有趣的
Yeah.
是啊
This is gonna be fun.
一定会很有趣的
My, that's a beautiful pen.
天哪  这笔真漂亮
Is it a montblanc?
它是万宝龙的吗
Uh, yeah. yeah, I've always wanted one. ah.
是啊  我一直想要一支
Well, I guess you can afford it now with your new raise.
我想你升职后  能买的起了
Oh, you heard about that?
-你听说了吗
I sure did.
我当然听说了
Well, the chamber of commerce just called.
商会刚打来电话
They've added 40 people to their guest list.
说他们在客人名单上加进去40个人
Damn it. I only planned for a hundred.
妈的  我以为就100个人呢
W-we're gonna need tables. relax. they always pull this crap.
我们需要桌子  放轻松  他们总是搞这种烂事出来
So I called the rental company
我去打给租赁公司
And had 'em put a few extras on the truck. we'll be fine.
让他们多装些在卡车里  我们没问题的
Oh, thank god. but you know what?
谢天谢地  可你知道吗
We can tell the chamber people
我们该告诉商会那群人
That because it was so last-minute,
因为他们通知的太晚
We had to bump our fee by 30%.
-我们得提价百分之三十
I like the way you think.
我喜欢你的观点
Ohh. what would we do without him?
没了他  我们可怎么办
Hmm, yes. he's worth every penny you pay him.
是啊  他值得起你付的每一分工钱
By the way... how many pennies is that?
顺便问一句  到底有多少哇
I'm not discussing andrew's salary with you.
我不会跟你讨论安德鲁的工钱的
It's none of your business.
这与你无关
You're right. it's not.
你是对的  与我无关
So... how much?
那到底是多少呢
Andrew moved into a new home.
安德鲁搬进了新家
I simply gave him a cost of living increase.
我当然要给他加生活费了
The cost of living in a home
给一个用银质笔喝稀有法国红酒
With silver pens and rare french wines?
加家庭生活费吗
Honey, please don't do this.
亲爱的  请别这么说
Oh, my god. is he making more than me?
他赚的比我多吗
Orson, drop it.
奥森  别说了
I am not telling you how much andrew makes.
我不会告诉你安德鲁赚多少钱的
I'd be happy to give you that information, sir.
很乐意向您提供有关信息  先生
Am I speaking to the account holder?
您是她的账户持有人吗
No, I'm her... business partner.
不  我是她的合伙人
Very well. Account number?
好的  账号多少
Yes. Um, 8-5-9-7-3.
有  85973
Name on the account?
开户名
Van De Kamp's old-fashioned foods.
布里·范德坎普怀旧料理
and the password?
密码呢
Password?
还有密码吗
For security purposes.
为了安全起见
Oh. Yes. Of course. It's, um...
对  当然有  密码是
Uh, you know...
那个
Uh, it's--it's completely slipped my mind.
一下子想不起来了
It's the name of her childhood pet.
密码是她小时候养的宠物的名字
Oh. Right.
对了
Fluffy.
毛球
Nope. That's not it.
不对  不是这个
Fido?
淘淘
No.
不是
Spot? Rover?
点点  小野
Mittens?
手套
Sorry, sir.
先生  很抱歉
Uh, Marmaduke.
玛玛杜克
Old yeller.
大黄
I cannot give out any information
如果没有密码  我就无法透露任何信息
Without the password, which you obviously don't know.
很明显  你不知道密码
Then ask me a different question.
换个问题问我
How about her date of birth? Her social security number?
比如她生日  或者社会保险号码
Good-bye, sir.
再见 先生
How about her real hair color?
你知道她头发真正的颜色吗
Trust me, it's not what you think it is.
相信我  不是你知道的那个颜色
If you're looking to get fed, it's gonna be a while.
你们要是饿了  还得多等一会儿
No, dad called a family meeting.
不是饿  是爸爸说要开家庭会议
Yeah, mom, he said it's about the restaurant.
是  妈妈  他说要谈谈餐馆的事
Oh, boy. I think I know what this is about.
天哪 我知道他要说什么
Listen, kids,
孩子们  听我说
Things have been tough down at the restaurant,
餐馆最近经营不太好
and I think your dad has finally decided to sell it.
我猜你们爸爸终于决定要卖掉它了
I know.
我也很难过
Is he gonna be okay?
他还好吗
I don't know. That's why we all have to be really supportive.
我不知道  所以我们一定要支持他
Are you with me?
你们同意吗
Hey, guys.
大家好
Good. you're all here.
很好  大家都在
I love you, daddy.
我爱你  爸爸
Not yet.
说早了
So... I wanted to talk to you all about our pizzeria.
是这样  我想跟大家说说咱们的披萨餐馆
Just know we're 100% behind you.
记住  我们百分之百支持你
That means a lot,
那最好了
'cause this was a really rough day for me.
这段日子我过得很不容易
I had to let all our employees go.
我不得不遣散所有的伙计
So starting tomorrow...
所以从明天开始
You kids are my new waitstaff.
孩子们  你们来当新服务生
Tom, what the hell are you talking about?
汤姆  你这是说什么呢
I got it all worked out. You and I will handle the days,
我都想好了  白天就咱们俩
And the kids will join us after school and on the weekends.
等放学和周末  孩子们就来帮咱俩
Um, at the risk of sounding spoiled... no.
虽然会被你认为娇气  我还是要说我不去
Come on! It'll be fantastic. We'll love working together.
来吧  肯定超级棒  我们不是都喜欢工作在一起吗
Why? We don't even like living together.
谁说的  我们甚至都不愿意住在一起
Look, labor is our number one cost.
想想  工资是我们最大一项支出
If we can eliminate it, we'll start making a profit again.
如果我们不用花钱雇人  就又可以盈利了
What, you're not even gonna pay us?
不是吧  你连工资都不给我们发
I'm 9! Is that even legal?
我才9岁  打工合法吗
I think so.
挺合法的吧
But just to be safe, you're now 15. Happy birthday!
不过为了安全起见  我们就说你15岁了  生日快乐
Mom, please do something.
妈妈  你管管他啊
I thought maybe after our conversation today,
我以为今天跟你谈了之后
you'd realize it's time to pack it in.
你能真正意识到该放弃这种想法了
I have got to do this. I can't walk away from that place
我必须这么做  我没法甩袖子走人
until I have done everything that I can possibly think of.
至少要把能想到的办法都试一试
But having the kids work there?
那也不用让孩子们干活吧
You said that you were behind me 100%.
你不是说百分之百支持我吗
Really? That doesn't sound like me.
我说了吗  不像我说的话啊
Lynette...
勒奈特
Okay. Fine.
好吧  好
Kids, we are going to support your father
孩子们  我们为了要支持爸爸
by working in his restaurant.
得去餐馆帮忙
You've got to be kidding me.
你不是逗我玩吧
Just so you know, 30 years from now,
我得跟你说明白  今后30年
When you and dad are old and feeble
你和爸爸要是年老力衰
You're putting us
就把我们送去
in the cheapest nursing home you can find.
最便宜的养老院
Yeah, I got it.
好  我明白
Mrs. Solis, I didn't realize you were here.
索利斯太太  才发现您来了
I've got your bracelet all polished
您的手镯已经清洗干净
and ready for a night on the town.
您晚上去城里玩的话能戴了
Oh, I'll put it on and have a good time.
我以后会戴着它出去的
Turns out I'm not gonna be able to afford it right now...
事实上  我目前还买不起
unless you can help me out on the price.
除非你能在价格上再帮帮忙
What did you have in mind?
你有什么想法
You give it to me,
把它给我
and then call your insurance and say it was stolen?
然后打电话给你的保险公司  说手镯被盗
I didn't think so.
我随便说说而已
I'm really sorry about the bracelet, Mrs. Solis.
索利斯太太  对于手镯的事我很抱歉
Perhaps I can show you something a bit less expensive.
不过我给你看看比它便宜点的吧
Maybe some, uh, earrings
可以试试  耳环
Oh, will you excuse me a minute?
能不能等我一下
Carlos, get in here!
卡洛斯  过来
I got a real shockeroo for you!
我有爆炸性新闻
You are not gonna believe this!
你肯定不信
Brad! Hi.
布莱德  你好
Uh, what's going on?
什么事
He just stopped by with great news.
他带来了特大新闻
I'm getting that bonus after all.
公司要发奖金给我了
Really?
真的吗
Well, I went to our C.F.O.,
我跟财政总监见了个面
and I told him it just didn't seem fair
跟他说太不公平了
that my right-hand man should go unrewarded.
怎么能不给我的左膀右臂发奖金呢
Isn't that great? What kind of guy does that?
这简直太好了  这得是多好一个人啊
Oh, I think I know the kind.
我知道他能好的什么程度
So, Brad...
那么  布莱德
What sort of bonus are we looking at?
这次奖金有多少呢
How does 20 grand sound?
2万美元怎么样
Like a great jumping off point.
这是起拍价吗
Gaby.
加布
Oh, honey, you heard Maria the other night.
亲爱的  你那天不是听玛利亚说了吗
Your hard work is what's brought them so much closer.
多亏了你  他们夫妻俩才更加更加亲密
Pay no attention to my wife.
当作没听见
20 grand is a fantastic bonus.
2万已经是超级大红包了
You know, now that I hear the number out loud,
听你这么大声一说
It does seem a little low, after all you've done.
的确奖金跟你们做的比还不够
25 is probably more fair.
2万5还差不多
Oh, Brad. Come on. Saving a marriage?
布莱德  不是吧  我们拯救了你的婚姻
You can't put a price on that...
这可是无价的
at least not a small one.
怎么说也不是小数目
Gaby, will you knock it off?
加布  你能不能别闹了
You're being rude.
你这样太没礼貌了
You're right. I'm sorry.
你说的对  对不起
It's just--I really wanted to buy this bracelet I saw today
我只是  非常想买今天在城里一家小珠宝店
downtown in this little jewelry shop.
看中的一只手镯
You know the place, honey.
亲爱的  你知道地方
It's right next to the, um...
就是挨着  那个
Lexington hotel.
莱克星顿大酒店
30!
三万
$30,000.
三万美元
Are you sure?
真的假的
Yes! You deserve it. You both do.
真的  这是你应得的  你们俩
I don't know what to say.
我都不知道怎么感谢你了
You're the only one getting a bonus,
你是唯一一个得奖金的
so what I think might be best is
所以我觉得
if we all agreed not to say anything.
咱们几个最好都别跟别人说
Do we all agree?
说好了
Absolutely.
确定一定以及肯定
Now if you'll excuse me, I'll leave you two to business.
失陪了  不打扰你们俩谈生意
All this negotiating just goes right over my head.
这次协商我早就知道能行
Thunder Mcfadden. What a hoot.
雷公·麦法登  一听就是个大嗓门
What's that?
什么东西
Oh, it's my porn name.
是我的AV艺名
A friend sent me an e-mail.
我朋友给我发了个电邮
You take the name of your childhood pet
填上小时候宠物的名
and the street you grew up on, and voila?
再填上小时候在哪条街长大的  就这样
That's the name you'd use if you were a porn star.
就出来了你当艳星要用的艺名
So I'm Thunder Mcfadden.
我的是雷公·麦法登
My buddy here is Snoop Windemere.
我朋友叫史努比·文德米尔
Hey, who would you be?
看看你会是谁
Orson, I'm preparing a buffet for 200.
奥森  我在为200人准备自助餐
I don't have time to explore
我可没功夫探索
my hypothetical career in the adult film industry.
我在成人电影行业的假想职业生涯
Fine.
好吧
But you should know that's why people find you so rigid,
你该知道为什么别人总说你呆板了吧
because you can never just let go and have fun.
你从来都不懂今朝有酒今朝醉
Coco saugatuck. Happy now?
宠物叫可可  住在索加塔克街  你满意了吧
Sure am.
非常开心
Thanks, hon.
谢啦  亲亲
Of course it could just as easily be Munchy cedarhurst
当然  也可能是小饕  香柏堤街
What?
什么
or Taffy swallow.
或者是甜甜和飞燕街
We moved around a lot and had three dogs.
我们家总搬家  而且养过3条狗
Bree, focus.
布里  用点心
It has to be your favorite pet.
一定得是你最喜欢的那条狗
Like if I asked you, "what's your childhood pet?"
就像别人问你  你小时候养的狗叫什么
This is the one you'd say.
你说的那条就是
I didn't really have a favorite. I loved them all equally.
我没有什么最喜欢的  我都喜欢
Oh, please. If Coco, Taffy and Munchy were
拜托  如果房子着火了
in a burning building and you could only save one...
可可  甜甜  小饕  你只能救一只
Orson, why are you being so morbid?
奥森  你今天很不正常
No.  I- I just want to know your porn name.
不是  我只是想看看你的AV艺名
Okay, fine.
好吧
If I had to pick a favorite, I guess it would be Munchy.
如果非要我选个第一  我就选小饕吧
She was a bit rambunctious.
她有点淘气
Father sent her to a farm so she'd have room to run.
所以爸爸把她送到乡下  地方大  够她跑
I cried for weeks and weeks.
我哭了好几个礼拜
Munchy, huh? This was fun.
小饕  真有趣
All right, that's a large mushroom pepperoni pizza
好吧  大号蘑菇意大利香肠披萨
and two salads. I'll get that started.
两份沙拉  马上就好
- Tom, I got need a large
-汤姆  我要一个大...
Large pep/mush at table nine.
9号桌大蘑肠
I'm way ahead of you.
抢先一步
Thanks. And do you have the calzones for table three?
非常感谢  3号桌烤乳酪馅饼好了吗
- Oh, crap.
-糟了
Sweetie, I need two dinner salads.
亲爱的  我要两份沙拉
What's the matter?
怎么了
Parker said the only reason you had me make salads
帕克说你让我做沙拉就是因为
is because it's a job for babies.
做沙拉是小儿科
Well, clearly, that's not true because you're not a baby.
很显然他说的不对  你才不是小儿科呢
You're 15, remember?
你15岁了  对不对
Also, I can't find my band-aid.
我的创可贴不知道掉哪碗里了
Okay, you fill water glasses. I'll make the salads.
好吧  你去倒水  我来做沙拉
- Hey, mom?
-妈妈
Yeah?
什么事
This is for table five.
这是5号桌的
Oh, thanks.
谢谢
Uh... you didn't give them enough change.
你找钱找少了
Yeah, I know. I figured this out.
我知道  我发现的
You can short people 1%, and they won't even notice.
少给客人找1%零钱  他们根本发现不了
If they got a buzz on, 3%.
如果他们说得热火朝天  就扣3%
Okay, you make the salads.
好吧  你做沙拉
I'll handle the register.
我来收银
Dude, back off. That's my table.
老弟  走开  这是我的客人
Not anymore. You can take the 4-top of old farts.
现在不是了  你去招呼4号桌那个老屁
- No way. I
-没门  我...
What's going on?
发生什么了
He took my table.
他抢我客人
So? Take another one. What's the difference?
那又怎样  换个客人  有什么不一样
Well, since I'm the only one here who can wait on that table
好吧  只有我去招待那位客人
without knocking over a glass with my pants,
才不会让裤子把玻璃杯刮掉地上
how about I take it?
我去接待怎么样
You handle the cash register. You bus tables. Go on.
你收银  你推餐车  动起来
Well, look at this.
哇  你看看
Everybody's happy.
大家都那么高兴
Things are running smoothly.
一切都一帆风顺
Don't worry. I'm not gonna say, "I told you so."
别担心  我不会跟你说那句  我早就告诉过你
Hey. Katherine said you wanted to talk to me.
凯瑟琳说你想跟我谈谈
Yeah. Come on in.
对  快进来吧
You know, you could have just called.
你打个电话就行了
You don't have to use her as an intermediary.
不用让她传话
Really? I thought we were using Katherine
是吗  我觉得咱俩都在利用凯瑟琳
for all sorts of things-- sending messages,
很多事情上都是  比如传话
raising our kid.
抚养孩子
I don't see what the big deal is.
我不觉得有什么大问题
I have to work, and she has some free time.
我得工作  而她恰好有空
It's better for everybody.
对大家都好
Well, it's not better for me,
这么说吧  对我不好
especially when I'm not even told about it.
尤其是你们都不提前说一声
Fine. Here I am telling you.
好吧  那我现在跟你说一声
I have to work Friday,
我周五要工作
so Katherine will be picking M.J. up from school.
所以凯瑟琳去接M.J.放学
No.
不行
What do you mean, "no"?
什么意思
Let me remind you, I have custody on Fridays.
提醒你一下  我每周五都禁足
Hey, thanks. Let me remind you
谢谢提醒  我也得提醒你一下
that the reason I agreed to custody is
我之所以同意禁足
so our son could spend time with his father.
是为了让我儿子有机会跟他父亲相处
You have a problem with Katherine?
你对凯瑟琳有意见吗
No, she's a peach,
不  她人见人爱
but she's not the one that dragged me to court
不过她不是把我拽到法庭上
to hammer out some custody agreement.
煞费苦心弄出个禁足条例的人
Now if you'd like, we can go back,
如果你不愿意  我们可以再回去
and the judge can explain to you
法官会给你好好解释一下
the difference between you and your girlfriend.
你和你女朋友到底有什么不同
Okay, you listen to me.
好吧  听我说
Mommy?
妈妈
Are you guys fighting?
你们在吵架吗
No, sweetie.
没有  宝贝
We are just trying to figure out what is best for you.
我们只是在讨论怎么做是对你最好
aren't we?
是不是
I'll see you friday, buddy.
周五见  儿子
Looks like I'll be picking you up from school.
我会去接你放学
Andrew makes twice as much as me?
安德鲁比我多挣两倍
Who told you that?
谁告诉你的
A little bird
一只小鸟
Or should I say a little dog named munchy?
我还知道有一只叫小饕的小狗
That's why you wanted to know the names of my pets?
这就是为什么你想知道我宠物的名字
Orson hodge, you are shameful.
奥森·霍吉  你真可耻
What's shameful is how much you're paying him.
你给他那么多钱才可耻呢
Andrew has been with me since I launched the company.
安德鲁是公司的开朝元老
He runs every aspect of the business.
他管理公司的每个部门
He deserves what he's making.
他应得那么多钱
but I am your husband, for crying out loud.
可我是你老公  工作是哭着得来的
Yes, orson,
是的  奥森
we're all aware of how you got the job.
我们都清楚你是怎么得到这份工作的
You know what the real travesty is?
你知道最讽刺的是什么吗
I'm more educated than the lot of you.
我比你们学历都高
I went to grad school. I'm a dentist.
我读了研究生  是个牙医
no, you were a dentist.
不  你曾经是个牙医
Now you're a caterer, and you're paid fairly
现在你是个宴会承包商  工资合理
Based on your expertise and contribution.
基于你的专长和贡献
Oh, this is not about money, bree. it's about value.
布里  这与钱无关  是关于价值
And you're saying I'm worthless.
你是说我不值
No, I'm just saying you're worth... less.
我只是说你值得...少一点
I'm sorry, honey.
抱歉  亲爱的
I'm just being honest.
我说的是实话
Very well.
好吧
Oh, since we're being honest,
既然我们坦诚相待
munchy didn't go to any farm.
告诉你  小饕没去什么去农场
That's what parents tell their kids
当孩子沉迷于宠物时
When they just had their pets gassed.
父母都是这么说的
Hi. you got a minute?
有空吗
I have a really big favor to ask you.
我有事问你
Uh, sure.
可以
I need a little detective work done.
我请了私家侦探
It's about bradley.
关于布拉德利的
So...
然后呢
What's going on?
怎么回事
I'm gonna buy a golf club.
我打算买个高尔夫俱乐部
A baseball bat would be cheaper.
棒球球棒更便宜点
Maybe I should let you finish.
我该让你把话说完
See, I don't know anything about golf clubs,
你看  我对高尔夫俱乐部一无所知
But I know carlos does,
可是卡洛斯很在行
So I was hoping you guys could snoop around
所以我希望你们帮忙打听一下
And find out what kind of driver brad wants.
看看布拉德想要什么样的司机
Oh, it's a gift.
这是个礼物啊
Sure, yeah.
好啊
We'd love to help out.
我们愿意帮忙
So what's the occasion? no occasion.
为什么这么做呢  没有原因
I just want to thank him for being a wonderful husband.
我只是想谢谢他  他是个好丈夫
Well, don't spend too much.
不用花这么多钱吧
Why don't you just get him a card?
为什么不给他张卡呢
So our marriage counselor said we should get each other
婚姻顾问说  我们应该自然的
Little gifts now and then to keep things spontaneous.
经常给对方礼物
Oh, you're in counseling. that's great.
你在咨询顾问  太好了
We were, but we stopped. we don't need it anymore.
以前咨询过  不再需要了
Are you sure about that?
你确定吗
yeah. brad and I are solid.
是的  我和布莱德关系很稳定
Well, ice is solid, too,
在冰裂开  掉进冰水里之前
Until it cracks and you're drowning in freezing water.
冰也是很稳定
I'd stay in counseling if I were you.
我要是你  就继续进行咨询
Gaby, I'm home! can you come in here for a minute?
加布  我回来了  能过来一下吗
Brad gives me a huge bonus
布拉德给了我那么多奖金
and you repay him By telling his wife
你跟他老婆说他们的婚姻需要咨询
that they need marriage counseling?
来作为报答吗
I'm sorry. I think they do.
真抱歉  我觉得他们需要
Their marriage is none of your business.
人家的婚姻问你没关系
Besides, I think they're a very happy couple.
另外  我觉得他们是幸福的一对
who? him and maria
谁  他和玛利亚
Or him and the blonde I saw him kissing yesterday?
还是那个金发女郎  我昨天看见他们接吻了
What? no way!
什么  不可能
Yeah. and brad saw me.
是的  布拉德也看见我了
Why do you think your bonus jumped
你觉得你的奖金为什么会
From a stuffed chicken breast to 30 grand in a day?
从一个烤鸡胸涨到一天三万美元
Oh, my god.
天哪
This is illegal.
这是违法的
I'm getting a bonus no one else is getting
我得奖金而别人没有奖金
based on blackmail.
居然是因为用了勒索
You're welcome.
不用客气
I can't believe you did this.
真不该相信你竟然会这么做
Well, thank god you came to your senses.
好吧  感谢上帝你想到解决办法了
All right, let's get in there and tell her.
好吧  我们进去告诉她
No, we can't tell her. we'd have to give the money back.
不  不能跟她说  我们还得把钱还回去
Don't we have a moral responsibility to tell her?
我们有道义要告诉她吗
It's like you said--
就像你说的
Their marriage is none of our business.
他们的婚姻问我们没关系
He's the one who's cheating.
他是不忠的那一个
If we say anything, it'll just make things worse.
如果我们透露风声  只会让事情变得更糟
We're the good guys here, carlos.
卡洛斯我们是好人
Really? 'cause it sure doesn't feel like it.
是吗  感觉不太像
It's open.
门开着
Susan, you got our message.
苏珊  你收到消息了
Yes, and imagine my surprise,
是的  想不到我有多吃惊
'cause the last time I talked to mike,
最后一次跟麦克说话
He promised me he was picking up m.j. from school.
他答应我会接M.J放学的
Oh, mrs. nelson had another plumbing emergency.
尼尔森夫人又有一个水管坏了
Apparently this new oat bran diet she's on--
显然她的燕麦片节食...
I don't need the details. I had a long day.
我不想知道细节  我今天很累
I just want to pick up my kid.
我只是过来接孩子的
Mommy, we had paninis for dinner. you want one?
妈妈  我们晚餐做的意式三文治  你想尝尝吗
No, thank you. let's go.
不用  走  回家
But we were gonna make brownies for dessert.
可是我们要做巧克力饼甜点
But we can make brownies at home.
我们在家里也可以做啊
The box kind? katherine says those aren't real brownies.
盒装的那种吗  凯瑟琳说那不是真正的巧克力饼
Except when your mommy makes them with love.
除非是你妈妈用爱心做的
Good save.
解释的不错
Let's go.
走吧
Susan?
苏珊
Look,
听着
I know you were surprised to find m.j. here again today,
我明白你发现M.J今天又在这里很奇怪
But I really was trying to do you a favor.
可我真的是想帮你
Well, I don't need you to do me any favors.
好吧  我不需要你帮我
What I need is for everyone to just stick to the plan.
我需要的是大家按计划行事
Monday, wednesday, friday-- mike watches his son.
周一  三  五  麦克看孩子
He doesn't pawn him off on his girlfriend.
而不是把孩子丢给他的女朋友
I had a really fun time.
我过的很开心
Big group coming in.
来了一大帮人
It is now officially saturday night.
周六的夜晚这才正式开始嘛
Finally.
终于来了
Oh, great. they're kids.
棒极了  是一群孩子
1 plate of spaghetti and 15 baskets of free bread.
点盘意面  再来15篮免费面包
Stop being such a downer.
别泼冷水了
We're finally making a go of this place.
我们在这儿的买卖  终于要有点起色了
All you want to do is complain.
而你想做的  就只是抱怨
We'r taking a break.
我们要休息一下
N-not now. we just got a big party.
现在不行  我们有场大派对要办
Good luck with that. we're outta here.
那祝你们好运了  我们要走了
What's going on here?
这是怎么了嘛
Those kids go our school.
那些小孩是我们学校的
And you know who that big guy is?
你知道那个大个儿是谁么
Kevin mcdermott. the guy called me "jesus" for a year
凯文·麦克德摩  就因为我有天穿了凉鞋
'cause I wore sandals one day.
他叫我耶稣  叫了一年
If he sees me wearing this, I'll never hear the end of it.
他看见我穿这个  他肯定要说个没完没了
Fine. don't wear that apron. that's...
-好吧  别穿这围裙了
no,
不行
I'm not waiting on a kid who's gonna
我是不会服侍一个
Make fun of me on monday morning.
打算在礼拜一早晨拿我找乐的小孩的
It's humiliating enough having to work here.
-在这儿干活就够丢人的了
humiliating?
丢人
Guys, easy. no,
伙计们  放轻松
You're-- you're not humiliated when you use the money that we make here
你们用在这儿赚到的钱买衣服时
To buy your clothes.
-可没觉得丢人啊
tom, it's fine. I'll take the table.
好了  汤姆  我去摆台
No, no, no, no, no, no. your mother can't wait
不  不  不  你们的妈妈不能一个人
- On this whole restaurant by herself.
-服侍整个餐馆的人
well, then you do it.-
那你去做呗
Porter, I'm your father and your boss,
波特  我是你爸  还是你老板
And I'm telling you right now to go take that table.
现在我告诉你  去摆台子
Or what, you're gonna fire me? go for it.
否则怎样  你要炒了我吗  尽管炒吧
You think this is a joke? this is my life!
你觉得这是个玩笑吗  这是我的生活
Tom!
-汤姆
you worry about being embarrassed?
你在担心感觉尴尬
I have put everything I have into this restaurant!
我可是把我的一切都赌在这餐馆上了
All right, that's enough!
好吧  够了
Let go of him! let go of him! let go of him!
放开他  放开他  放开他
Guys?
伙计们
I just sat a 12-top. who's taking it?
我刚摆了第12桌  谁去接手
I will.
我去
I started getting our accounts in order.
我要开始理理咱们的帐了
If we're gonna sell this place,
要是我们要卖这地方
We should probably know exactly how much it's worth.
我们该知道  它到底值多少钱
I think this can all wait until morning.
我想  这些可以等到明天再做
Don't you?
你觉得呢
Hey. I just booked us into the brunswick inn
我刚给咱俩订了布伦斯威克客栈
For this weekend.
去度周末
Great.
太棒了
Prepare to be pampered!
准备好食指大动吧
Oh, shoot.
不好
This weekend isn't gonna work.
这周末去不成啊
Mike really wants us to do that camping trip
那个我们说起过的野营
That we've been talking about.
迈克超想和咱俩一起去
Camping? have you met me?
野营  你不认识我了么
I figured you were gonna say that.
我就知道你会这么说
I just can't blow him off.
我就是没法让他扫兴
This is the only weekend that works for him.
这是他唯一有空的一个周末
Then you're on your own.
那你自己去呗
Have fun wiping with leaves.
-祝你扫树叶扫的愉快啊
oh, edie?
伊迪
Please don't tell katherine that you're not coming.
请别告诉凯瑟琳  你不来了
All right? mike really wants her there,
好吗  迈克很想让她一起去
And if she hears that you're not going, she won't either.
要是她听说你不去  她也不会去了
Will you take me
那你下周会带我
To the brunswick inn next weekend?
去布伦斯威克客栈吗
Yes.
当然
Then I won't say a word to katherine.
那我会对凯瑟琳守口如瓶
Hey. when did you two get here?
你俩什么时候到的
Just a minute ago.
刚到一会儿
They said they have something personal
他们说  有些私事
They want to talk to us about.
想告诉我们
Oh, really? what is it?
真的吗  是什么呀
We're pregnant.
我们有孩子了
I know. we are so happy.
我知道  我们太开心了
But that's not all.
还不止这些呢
See, even though
听着  虽然我们
We've only known each other for a short time,
认识的时间不长
Your friendship has meant a lot to us,
你们的友谊  对我们意义重大
Which is why maria feels strongly
所以玛利亚深切的感觉到
That you should be the baby's godparents.
应该让你们做孩子的教父母
Do you hear that, carlos?
你听到了吗  卡洛斯
Godparents.
教父母
You are such good people, so kindhearted and decent,
你们是多好的人啊  善良又得体
And that is the kind of influence
那正是我们想给我们孩子的人生
That we want in our baby's life.
带来的影响
How could we say no?
我们怎么能拒绝呢
Oh. I see you got your bracelet after all.
你还是得到了你的手镯啊
Oh, yeah.
是啊
Uh, but I'm not enjoying it as much as I thought I would.
可我没像想象中那么喜欢它
Okay, lunch and a movie. you are one lucky boy.
吃着午餐看电影  你可真是个幸运的孩子
I'm gonna take a quick shower.
我要赶快冲个凉
Try not to get any crumbs on the couch.
尽量别把碎屑掉在沙发上
What's wrong?
怎么了
It's peanut butter, no crusts--
是花生酱的  没有硬皮
Your favorite.
你的最爱哦
I want a panini.
我想吃的意式三文治
I don't know how to make paninis.
我不知道怎么做的意式三文治
It's just turkey and cheese.
就是火鸡跟奶酪嘛
Do we have any provolone?
咱家有波萝伏洛干酪吗
No, we do not have any provolone.
不  咱家没有波萝伏洛干酪
Can we borrow some from katherine?
咱们能跟凯瑟琳借点吗
Absolutely not.
绝对不能
In this house, we do not eat pretentious cheeses.
在这个房子里  我们不吃自命不凡的奶酪
We eat honest american peanut butter.
我们吃脚踏实地的美式花生酱
Now watch your movie,
现在看你的电影吧
And I'll be back in a minute.
我一会儿就来
Will you make me a panini?
你会给我做意式三文治吗
Uh, well, sure, sweetie.
当然了  亲爱的
Does your mommy know you're here?
你妈妈知道你在这儿吗
Hey, sweetie. how was your sandwich?
甜心  你的三明治怎么样
M.j.?
M.J
M.j., honey, where are you?
M.J  亲爱的  你在哪
M.j., where are you?!
M.J  你在哪
M.j.!
M.J
What is he doing here?
他在这儿干什么
He wanted a panini, said you knew.
他想吃意式三文治  说你知道的
M.j., go wait outside on the porch.
M.J  去门廊那边等着
I need to talk to katherine.
我得跟凯瑟琳谈谈
You can take the sandwich.
你可以把三文治带着走
Look, he showed up on my doorstep.
听着  他出现在我门前
He seemed hungry.
看起来很饿
You think I don't feed my kid?
你以为我不会喂饱我的孩子吗
Okay, well, maybe he just wanted to come see me.
好吧  也许他就是想来见我
Yeah, 'cause you make it like disneyland over here,
是啊  因为你用意式三文治跟海盗旗
With your paninis and your blackjack.
把这儿弄的跟迪士尼乐园似的
You're trying to do everything you can
你在尽你所能
To make him think that you're the other mommy.
让他以为  你是他另外一个妈妈
what?
啥
You're trying to get your hooks deeper into mike
你想向麦克展示  他儿子有多爱你
By showing him how much his son loves you.
好把他绑的更紧
susan, I am being nice
苏珊  我在好好对待
To the child of the man I'm dating.
我约会的男人的儿子
How does that make me evil?
就凭这怎么能让我成了个恶魔呢
No, not evil. devious.
不  不是恶魔  是卑鄙小人
Well, you know, I hate to tell you,
好吧  你知道  我也不想说这个的
But your big plan is not gonna work,
可你的大计划落空了
'cause from now on, m.j. is either at my house or mike's.
因为从现在起  M.J不是在我家  就是去麦克家
He is no longer allowed to be here.
他不许再来这儿了
yeah, uh, that's gonna be tricky.
这可就麻烦了
Well, that's the way it's gonna be, whether you like it or not.
只能这样  不管你喜不喜欢
No, it's gonna be tricky because mike's moving in here.
这就麻烦了  是因为麦克就要搬来这儿了
What?
什么
First of the month,
这个月一号
He's giving up his place and moving in with me.
他就不租他那房子  搬来跟我住了
So m.j. is going to be spending a lot of time here,
所以M.J将会在这里呆上很久哦
Whether you like it or not.
不管你喜不喜欢
Orson, I'm glad you're here.
奥森  真高兴你来了
I was doing a recount of the goblets
霍普金斯家的结婚茶会那案子
For the hopkins wedding reception,
我重新数了一下酒杯
And we're short by about 30... oh.
我们大概还缺30个
So I have to run over to the supplier
所以我得再去供应商那儿跑一趟
And pick up the rest.
把剩下的拿来
could you hold down the fort for me?
你能帮我撑一会儿吗
sure.No problem.
没问题
Thanks.
谢谢
hey, you know, andrew?
你知道吗  安德鲁
it never would have occurred to me
我从没想过
To do a recount of the goblets.
重新数一下酒杯
Bree's lucky to have
布里有你这样细心的人帮她
Someone as conscientious as you working here.
真是幸运之极
Wow. thank you, orson.
谢谢你  奥森
That-- that means a lot to me.
这话对我意义很重
It begins just after sunrise.
在太阳初升之后
After a good night's sleep,
经过一夜的好眠
People leave their homes to go to work.
人们纷纷离家  出门工作了
They do this so they can provide
人们工作  是为了给家人
A better life for their families...
提供更好的生活
Afford to buy nice things...
买的起漂亮的商品
And have a reason to get up in the morning.
有个早上起床的理由
And when their exhausting work is done,
当他们精疲力竭的结束工作
People come back home again...
再次回到家中
And some begin counting the days...
有些人开始亟不可待的计算起
Till their next vacation.
再次休假的时候